Well,I can go throuht the possible strategies with you and let you decide where to go from there. Okay,thanks.
我可以和你查阅一下可行的策略，让你决定里面哪个适合。好的，谢谢。
Well,some people find it helpful to organise peer-group discussions
有些人觉得组织同龄人的小组讨论很有帮助，
you know,each week a different person studies a different topic and shares it with the group.
每周由不同的人研究一个不同的话题并与小组的其他人分享。
Oh right. It really helps build confidence,you know,having to present something to others. I can see that.
是的。这对树立信心有帮助，把某些事情介绍给别人。我看得出来。
The drawback is that everyone in the group seems to share the same ideas...
缺点是小组里的每个人似乎都有相同的观点，
they keep being repeated in all the dissertations. Okay.
所有的论文都在重复这些观点。是的。
You could also try a service called 'Student Support'.
你还可以尝试一项“学生支持”服务。
It's designed to give you a structured programme over a number of weeks to develop your skills. Sounds good.
它通过几周的结构课程提升你的技能。听起来不错。
Yes,unfortunately there are only a few places.But it's worth looking into.
是的，不幸的是名额有限。但是值得尝试。
Yes,of course.I know I've got to work on my study skills.
当然。我知道我得改进我的学习技巧。
And then there are several study skills books you can consult. Right.
有一些学习技巧的书供你查阅。好的。
They'll be a  good source of reference but the problem is they are sometimes too general.
它们是很好的参考来源，但问题是范围有时太宽泛了。
Yes,that's what I've found.
是的，我也发现了。
Othe than that I would strongly advise quite simple ideas like using a card index.
除此之外，我强烈建议一些简单的主意，像是使用卡片索引。
Well,yes,I've never done that before.
是的，我之前从没试过。
It's simple,but it really works because you have to get points down in a small space.
它很简单，但是很有用，因为你不得不把要点写在一个小的空间上。
Another thing I always advise is don't just your notes and forget about them.
另一件我总是说的事是不要只记笔记而将它们抛在脑后。
Read everything three times-that'll really fix them in your mind.
每一个都读三遍，这能帮你记牢。
Yes,I can see it'd take discipline but... Well,if you establish good study skills at this stage they'll be with you all your life.
是的，我明白这个方法需要训练，但是……如果你在这个阶段养成了好的学习技巧，你将终生受用。
Oh yes.I completely agree. It's just that I don't seem to be able to discipline myself.
是的，我完全同意。但是我觉得我不能约束自己。
I need to talk things over.
我需要探讨这些事情。
Well,we'll be continuing these tutorials of course.
我们肯定会继续这些辅导。
Let's arrange next month's now.
让我们现在安排下个月的事情。
Let's see,I can see you virtually any time during the week starting 22nd January.
让我看看。我看到你从1月22日开始的那周都有空。
What about the 24th? I'm free in the afternoon.
24日怎么样？下午我有空。
Sorry,I'm booked then.
对不起，我有预约了。
What about the following day?
第二天怎么样？
Thursday?I can make the morning.
周四？我早上有空。
Fine,we'll go fo the 25th then. That's great,thanks.
好的，我们定在25日。太好了，谢谢。